<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Brian Ivan Cusuanto</title>
    <link>https://brdx88.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Brian Ivan Cusuanto</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://brdx88.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project 5: Fraudulent Transaction Detector</title>
      <link>https://brdx88.github.io/post/project-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brdx88.github.io/post/project-5/</guid>
      <description>Fraud has become a scandal in financial reporting. Evidently, many large companies were dragged into fraud cases such as SK Global, Vivendi, Enron, Parmalat, Adelphia, Cendant, WorldCom, and Royal Ahold (Albrecht, et al., 2008). Companies are caught up in the situation of business globalization which has triggered intense business competition. As a result, companies are looking for any way to keep their business operating properly and even become winners in global business competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 4: Predicting House Price for the Best Investment</title>
      <link>https://brdx88.github.io/post/project-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brdx88.github.io/post/project-4/</guid>
      <description>Home is a primary basic need, everyone needs a house for shelter every day. However, for those who have their needs met, some people use the money to invest. One of the investment instruments is property, especially houses. This dataset provides information on the number of bedrooms, bathrooms, conditions, views, building area, land area, basement area, and of course prices. The dataset can be found on Kaggle.
Problems Many people want to start investing but don&amp;rsquo;t know where to invest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Cancelation Factors and Resources Efficiency in Hotels</title>
      <link>https://brdx88.github.io/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brdx88.github.io/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>This data set contains booking information for a city hotel, a resort hotel, and includes information such as when the booking was made, length of stay, the number of adults, children, and/or babies, and the number of available parking spaces, among other things.
We found this data set on Kaggle but the data is originally from the article Hotel Booking Demand Datasets - ScienceDirect written in journal named Data in Brief, Volume 22, February 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Reasons Why the Customer Wants to Stop Saving at the Bank</title>
      <link>https://brdx88.github.io/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brdx88.github.io/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>The bank is an institution for us to do economic activities as customers. Many customers decide to quit and move to another bank for their own reasons. Are bank services a factor? Or an attractive promo or program that makes customers loyal?
Problems:  What is the reason why the customer wants to stop saving at the bank concerned? Does CC ownership affect account termination? What effect does CreditScore have on account termination?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 3: Predicting Customer Interest in Vehicle Insurance</title>
      <link>https://brdx88.github.io/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brdx88.github.io/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>The cllient is an Insurance company that has provided Health Insurance to its customers now they need your help in building a model to predict whether the policyholders (customers) from past year will also be interested in Vehicle Insurance provided by the company. This dataset can be found on Kaggle.
An insurance policy is an arrangement by which a company undertakes to provide a guarantee of compensation for specified loss, damage, illness, or death in return for the payment of a specified premium.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
